Guide to the Donald W. Baker College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection, 1950- 1969.
Baker, Donald W. College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection
- Catherine Fabricant, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00090)
  Description: Candid of Catherine Fabricant standing at banquet table with flowers on it.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 10.5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Racheal Gordon Krieger, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00091)
  Description: Racheal Gordon Krieger standing outside waving.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4.4" x 5.5", 1 print on paper
- 1961 JAVMA Picnic, 1961 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00092)
  Description: 1961 JAVMA Picnic, log sawing contest. Peter Olafson looks on with the crowd. See also VPC.00292 and VPC.00085
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" X 10, 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Racheal Gordon Krieger, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00093)
  Description: Racheal Gordon Krieger wading in a stream. Janette Fraser is in the background facing away from the camera
- L. Goodman and Lyle Compton, 1949 January 10 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00094)
  Description: Candid of L. W. Goodman class of 1926 and Lyle S. Compton, class of 1931.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 7.5" x 9.5", 1 print on paper, 2 prints on cardboard"
  Photographer (if other than Baker): John F. Brock, Photo Science Services
- Dr. John Halloran, ca. 1950s (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00095)
  Description: Candid of Dr. John Halloran, Class of 1939, standing in a lab coat and holding a pipe.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7.5", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Tom Brown and others at a picnic, 1961 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00096)
  Description: Tom Brown, Class of 1962, and others at a picnic. Brown is facing right, with someone's has a hand on his shoulder
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10" 5"" x 8"" 3" x 5", 3 prints on paper (one cropped)
- Lyle Compton and Fred Hoyt (Box 1, Folder VPC.00097)
  Description: Lyle Compton, class of 1931 and Fred Hoyt, class of 1933 at an Annual Conference. Both are looking at the camera. Hyt is holding a cigarette.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4.5" x 6", 1 print on paper
- Henry Doremus and Harris Groten, 1960 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00098)
  Description: Candid of Henry Doremus with Harris Groten at an Annual Conference. Both are laughing and facing the camera.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4.5" x 6",5" x7", 4 prints on paper [2 cropped]
- C. P. Zepp Sr., ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00099)
  Description: Candid of C. P. Zepp Sr. with a name tag on and smiling
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4" x 7.5", 1 print on cardboard
- George Burch and Donald Lein and unidentified woman, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00100)
  Description: Candid of George Burch (class of 1936), Donald Lein (class of 1957) and unidentified woman
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 9.5", 1 print on cardboard
- John Leahy, 1957 April (Box 1, Folder VPC.00101)
  Description: Candid of John Leahy sitting at a desk in his coveralls. Unidentified woman stands next to him.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 9.5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 cropped print on paper"
- Harry Hodges, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00102)
  Description: Candid of Harry Hodges laughing at an AVMA conference
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4" x 8", 2 prints on paper
- Dr. and Mrs. Henry Grossman, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00103)
  Description: Candid of Dr. and Mrs. Henry Grossman class of 1938, outside
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 7", 6" x 6.5", 2 prints on paper 1 print on cardboard
- Drs John Hokanson and Charles Leahy, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00104)
  Description: Drs John Hokanson and Charles Leahy. There is a map and a stamp machine behind them. One is holding an ice cream bar on a stick.
- Bruce Hull, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00105)
  Description: Candid of Bruce Hull, class of 1965, at the microscope
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Chris Haller, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00106)
  Description: Candid of Chris Haller at a New York State Veterinary Medical Society meeting. He is sitting in a chair with his legs crossed and one arm up, wearing a shiny suit.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 1 print on paper 1 print on cardboard
- Leonard Tyler and V. Tharp from Ohio, ca. 1940s (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00107)
  Description: Candid of Leonard L. Tyler, Class of 1930, and Vernon Tharp from Ohio State, Class of 1940.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 8", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- David E. Hughes, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00108)
  Description: Candid of David E. Hughes, class of 1951, standing in a paddock in coveralls with a flock of sheep
  Size and Number of Photographs: "6.5"" x 9.5"" 7" x 9", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Drs. Cap Fuller and George Wiswall, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00109)
  Description: Howard K. "Cap" Fuller, class of 1932, and George Wiswall, Class of 1940. Fuller is sitting with his arms crossed, Wiswall is wearing a bolo.
- Margaret O'Brien Combs, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00110)
  Description: Candid of Margaret O'Brien Combs, Class of 1940. She is wearing a matching sweater and hat with a tassel.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 10.5", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- John G. Marvin, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00111)
  Description: John G. Marvin, Class of 1930., standing in front of a bulletin board with a sign reading "Do you know how to call your fire department?"
- Herbert Gilman retirement party, 1962 July (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00112)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Herbert L. Gilman retirement party at Finger Lakes Raceway. Joseph C. O'Dea and S.J. Roberts are in uncropped prints. Gilman is wearing a lei and holding a check. Published in Ellis Leonard, "Veterinary Centennial in New York State," page 30
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9", 3.5" x 5, "4 prints on paper 1 print on cardboard
- Alberta Dent Shackleton, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00113)
  Description: Alberta Dent Shackleton, Cornell Class of 1920 (AB). Second wife of Horace E. Shackleton? Mary Moore (Veranus Moore's daughter) was the first. She died some time in the 1930s.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 9", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Unidentified woman, 1962 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00114)
  Description: An unidentified woman on an airplane. She is seated and leaning forward. She is also pictured in VPC.00747
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7.5" 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- John Bentinck-Smith, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00115)
  Description: John Bentinck-Smith speaking in front of a lab bench to a group of students. He is wearing a while lab coat and holding up a test tube.
- Alpha Psi House, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00116)
  Description: Exterior of Alpha Psi house in winter
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 1 print on particleboard
- Sidney Nusbaum, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00117)
  Description: Sidney Nusbaum pouring something from an Erenlmeyer flask over the sink. He is standing behind a lab bench, in front of a black board. The print is a reverse: the writing on the blackboard is a mirror image.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 8.5", 1 print on particle board
- President Eisenhower, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00118)
  Description: President Eisenhower petting a cow
- S. J. Roberts, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00119)
  Description: Candid of Stephen J. Roberts standing in a lab coat in front of numerous animal intestines.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 9", 2 prints on paper
- Spectators at some sort of event, ca. 1940s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00120)
  Description: 6 spectators (3 seated, 3 standing), including 2 women
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 9.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Drs. Hughes, Todd, Berdan and Brown, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00121)
  Description: Hughes (Donald V. Hughes, Class of 1937?), Todd (Quinton L Todd, Class of 1931?), Berdan (Leonard N. Berdan, Class of 1943?) and Harold Brown
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 9", 1 print on cardboard
- Robert Garcia with a sheep, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00122)
  Description: Candid of Robert Garcia and two unidentified men with a sheep
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 8.5", 1 print on paper
- John Donovan, ca. 1960s (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00123)
  Description: Candid of John Donovan making a speech at a convention. Painting of race horses in the background. Ellis Leonard’s list calls him "Exec. Secretary."
  Size and Number of Photographs: "7.5"" x 8.5"" 5" x 7", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Robert Metzgar and Cheney, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00124)
  Description: Candid of Robert Metzgar (class of 1932) and Cheney. "N.Y. State Mastits experts" is written on photograph
- Maxine Benjamin and John Bentinck-Smith, 1960 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00125)
  Description: Candid of Maxine Benjamin and John Bentinck-Smith. Both are wearing coats.
- George Shurtleff and unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00126)
  Description: George C. Shurtleff, Class of 1959, and unidentified man. Shurtleff is probably the one in a bow tie. They are at a table with an ashtray and flowers in a paneled room.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9" 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 2 prints on paper"
- Mr and Mrs. Shefford Miller, 1953 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00127)
  Description: Mr and Mrs. Shefford S. Miller standing outside wearing name tags at a New York State Veterinary Medical Society clambake in Syracuse. She is wearing a jacket with a double rows of buttons and carrying a purse. Published in Ellis Leonard, "Veterinary Centennial in New York State," Page 169
- Nate Coye, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00128)
  Description: Candid of Nate Coye, class of 1943
  Size and Number of Photographs: 3" x 7.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Ira Fowler, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00129)
  Description: Candid of Ira Fowler, Snyder Hill Farm Manager for 35 years, standing in front of a door, wearing a coat, plaid shirt and glasses.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 9", 1 print on paper
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00130)
  Description: Unidentified man looking to his right. Short hair, side part. Wearing a suit with a tie with dots and horizontal lines
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 8", 1 print on paper
- Dr. John Ray, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00131)
  Description: Dr. John Ray, KCVC Class of 1917. Standing, facing left, wearing a hat and glasses.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 10" x 11.5", 1 print on cardboard
- H. Grossman and McKown, 1962 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00132)
  Description: Candid of H. Grossman,class of 1938, and Dr. McKown, class of 1943 seated at a table in a paneled room. Grossman is writing on a paper
  Size and Number of Photographs: "7"" x 9.5"" 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Dr. J.H. Steele and unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00133)
  Description: Dr. J.H. Steele, MSU Class of 1941, and unidentified man in a lab. Unidentified man is wearing a while lab coat.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 10" x 10", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Myron G. Fincher and J. M. Delaney, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00134)
  Description: Candid of M. G. Fincher and J. M. Delaney
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 7", 1 print on cardboard
- Mrs. Batchelder, Mrs. Lowe and unidentified women, 1964 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00135)
  Description: Candid of Mrs. Batchelder, Mrs. Lowe and an unidentified woman sitting on a sofa. Three other unidentified women are standing behind them. See also VPC.00678.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "8.5"" x 7"" 3" x 5", 3 prints on paper
- Dr. and Mrs. D. Hopkins, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00136)
  Description: Candid of Dr. and Mrs. David. Hopkins, Class of 1930
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 7.5", 2 prints on cardboard
- Veterinarians on a train, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00137)
  Description: Veterinarians on a train (presumably) on the way to a conference -- the first seat is a woman who is has her back toward the photographer. In the seat behind her are 2 men. One is looking to his left, the other has his hand near his chin and possibly ta
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 9", 1 print on cardboard
- The McClellands, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00138)
  Description: Frank McClelland, Class of 1909, Robert McClelland, Class of 1934, and Alfred H. McClelland, Class of 1912
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 10", 1 print on paper
- Dr. Das? and an unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00139)
  Description: Candid in a classroom with Das (?) and unidentified man
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 8.5", 1 print on cardboard
- John Bentinck-Smith and Stephen Roberts, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00140)
  Description: Candid of John Bentinck-Smith and Stephen Roberts standing in front of an exhibit which says "Veterinary Medicine--A career with a future" Probably Annual Conference.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 8" x 10", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- S. J. Roberts, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00141)
  Description: Candid of S. J. Roberts on the beach in a bathing suit
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 9.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Unidentified woman and Miss Halat (Box 1, Folder VPC.00142)
  Description: Candid of unidentified woman and Miss Halat sitting on a couch. Unidentified woman is wearing a coat.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 8", 1 print on cardboard
- Ira Fowler, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00143)
  Description: Ira Fowler, Snyder Hill Farm Manager for 35 years, wearing a suit, watching a talk. Myron Fincher is visible in the background.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "3"" x 4.5"" 8" x 10" 7"" x 9.5""", 3 prints on paper
- 3 unidentified people, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00144)
  Description: 2 men and a woman standing in front of a car. The man on the left is holding a pipe. Woman is holding a fringed bag with a woman on it. All 3 have name tags on.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "8.5"" x 10"" 8" x 10" (cropped) 6"" x 9"" (cropped)", 1 print on paper, 2 prints on cardboard"
- Judith Scanlon and unidentified man, 1962 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00145)
  Description: Candid of Judith Scanlon, class of 1963, and an unidentified man with a rabbit.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 9.5", 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Dr. VanValkenburg, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00146)
  Description: Dr. VanValkenburg of Texas
- Norman Seibert, January 1963 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00147)
  Description: Candid of Norman E. Seibert, class of 1938, seated with a cigar in hand, laughing with an unknown woman holding a purse, probably at his 25th class reunion. See also VPC.00075, VPC.00119, VPC.00159, VPC.00477, and VPC.00478.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "3" x 5" 5.5"" x 7"" (Norman only), 8" x 10" (Norman and woman)", 3 prints on paper
- Ira Fowler and R. R. Birch, ca. 1960s (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00148)
  Description: Ira Fowler (left) at his retirement. R. R. Birch (right) is presenting a book. See also VPC.00178.
- M. G. Fincher, ca. 1960s (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00149)
  Description: Candid of M. G. Fincher, with arms crossed, at a picnic
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9.5", 3 prints on cardboard, 2 transparencies"
- Edward C. Melby, Jean Melby and unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00150)
  Description: Edward C. Melby, Jean Melby and unidentified man standing in a parking lot in the snow.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 7", 1 print on paper
- Wedding couple dancing, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00151)
  Description: Wedding couple dancing. See similar photo: VPC.00133
- George Poppensiek and unidentified woman, 1964 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00152)
  Description: George Poppensiek and unidentified woman seated at a dinner table. Both are laughing. Man is wearing a suit and has dark, thick-rimmed glasses. The woman is wearing a white suit jacket
  Size and Number of Photographs: "9.5"" x 8"" 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- An airplane named the "Far Above", ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00153)
  Description: An airplane named the "Far Above"
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 7", 1 print on cardboard
- An airplane named the "Far Above", ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00154)
  Description: Close-up of the Cornell logo on the tail of the "Far Above."
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7.5", 1 prints on cardboard
- Unidentified men at a conference or meeting, ca. 1950s (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00155)
  Description: Unidentified men at a conference or meeting. 12 men are visible. One is turning back toward the camera. There is an exit door in the background.
- Drs. Pyles, Herrick, Payne, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00156)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Pyles, Dr. Herrick, and Dr. Payne
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9", 2 prints on cardboard
- M. Hortense Rowan and Larry Smith, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00157)
  Description: Mary Hortense Ford Rowan and Larry Smith standing outside under a tree. Cars in the background. See also UN-278
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 8", 1 print on paper
- Drs Rowan, Jaconson and Boroson, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00158)
  Description: Mary Hortense Ford Rowan, Louis H. Jacobson, and Elihu H. Boroson, all Class of 1953, standing outside. There is a car in the background. She is wearing a skirt, socks and loafers. UN-279
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 13", 1 print on paper
- Dr. David Hopkins, 1963 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00159)
  Description: Candid of Dr. David Hopkins, class of 1930, probably at the class of 1938's 25th reunion. See also VPC.00075, VPC.00119, VPC.00147, VPC.00477, and VPC.00478.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10" 5"" x 7"" 3" x 5", 3 prints on paper, 2 prints on cardboard"
- Dr. R. R. Birch, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00160)
  Description: Candid of Dr. R. R. Birch about to throw a horse shoe in the park
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5.5" x 8.5", 1 print on paper
- Dr. Caul? (Baton Rouge) dissecting zebra, 1962 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00161)
  Description: Dr. Caul? (Baton Rouge) dissecting zebra. He is bending slightly at the waist.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "3" x 5" 7" x 9", "2 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Dr. Caul? (Baton Rouge) dissecting zebra, 1962 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00162)
  Description: Dr. Caul? (Baton Rouge) dissecting zebra. He is standing, tongue stuck out.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 2 prints on cardboard
- Class of 1954, ca. 1954 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00163)
  Description: Candid shot of photo shoot for Class of 1954 portrait. Photographer is in the shot.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 6.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Schurman Hall winter scene, 1963 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00164)
  Description: Snowy pine tree with snow on the ground. Schurman Hall in the background
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper, 1 transparency"
- Students on lawn, ca. 1963 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00165)
  Description: Students on lawn, class of 1963, with a white dog
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 8" x 10", 3 prints on cardboard
- Unidentified woman and Mrs. Peckham, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00166)
  Description: Unidentified woman and Mrs. Peckham
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 7.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Harold Nadler, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00167)
  Description: Head shot of Harold Nadler, class of 1939
- F. S. Graziadei, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00168)
  Description: Candid of Frank S. Graziadei, class of 1929
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9", 2 prints on cardboard
- Dr. Caul? (Baton Rouge) dissecting zebra, 1962 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00169)
  Description: Dr. Caul? (Baton Rouge) dissecting zebra. He is standing, tongue in.
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00170)
  Description: Close up of an unidentified man looking down, facing to the left. He has thick-rimmed glasses on and a light patterned shirt
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 9 ", 1 print on cardboard
- Dr. and Mrs. Hopkins and S. J. Roberts, ca. 1965 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00171)
  Description: Candid of Dr. and Mrs. David Hopkins, class of 1930 and S. J. Roberts, class of 1938
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5" 3" x 5", "3 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Dr. Vaughn and students, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00172)
  Description: Dr. Vaughn and students dissecting an animal
  Size and Number of Photographs: Size:7.5" x 9.5", 1 print on cardboard
- 3 unidentified men with a foal, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00173)
  Description: 3 unknown men with a horse in a parking lot. One is taking vital signs, the other 2 are black. See also VPC.00174.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 8", 1 print on cardboard
- Jack Lowe, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00174)
  Description: Jack Lowe, Class of 1956, Standing in a parking lot with a horse. See also VPC.00173.
- Myron Fincher on the phone, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00175)
  Description: Myron Fincher on the phone.
- Myron Fincher talking with three others at a party, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00176)
  Description: Myron Fincher talking with two unidentified women and a man at a party. One woman has her back turned to the camera. The other woman is carrying a large purse.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6" x 7", 4"" x 7""", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard (cropped)"
- Savoyan, Burkhart and Fabricant, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00177)
  Description: Drs. Martin Sevoian (Penn 1953), Burkhart and Fabricant at Annual Conference [left to right].
  Size and Number of Photographs: "7.5"" x 10"" 1"" x 1.5""", 1 print on cardboard, 2 print on paper"
- Ira Fowler's retirement, ca. 1960s (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00178)
  Description: Ira Fowler talking to an unidentified man and woman at his retirement party. See also VPC.00148.
- Ab Quin, Kester, and unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00179)
  Description: Candid of Abe H. Quinn, W. O. Kester and unidentified man. Kester has his hands in his pockets
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7.5", 2 prints on paper 1 print on cardboard [cropped]"
- Dr. Edward R. Frank, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00180)
  Description: Dr. Edward R. Frank, of Kansas State, standing by a cattle photo exhibit with a shovel
  Size and Number of Photographs: "8.5 "" x 11"" 10"" x 9""--fine 10"" x 3""--fine", 1 print on paper 3 prints on cardboard, 1 cropped print on paper"
- 6 unidentified men (Box 1, Folder VPC.00181)
  Description: 6 men standing outside, 2 are looking to the left (one wearing a cowboy hat), one is looking at the photographer, another 2 are facing left, the last man is in the shadows
- Henry Grossman and unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00182)
  Description: Candid of Henry E. Grossman, Class of 1938, and unidentified man bending over a table. Grossman is holding a cigar. See also VPC.00192.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9", 1 print on cardboard (cropped), 1 print on paper
- Dr. and Mrs. Anison Lewis, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00183)
  Description: Candid of Dr. and Mrs. Anson "Scoop" Lewis, class of 1950
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 10", 1 print on cardboard
- Gugliemino [Williamson?] and Vince Peppe, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00184)
  Description: Gugliemino [Williamson] (Class of 1941) and Vince Peppe (Class of 1941)
- Commencement 1955, 1955 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00185)
  Description: Parents and students at a commencement event 1955. Includes Thomas W. Garbutt, John W. Flemer, and Robert W. Kirk. Taken in the Moore Laboratory.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x8", 1 prints on cardboard